Sol M. Linowitz Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Office File, 1778-1999 (Box 136-538)
  - Part A, 1778-1967 (Box 136-291)
    - Harris, Beach, Keating, Wilcox, Dale, and Linowitz (law firm), Rochester, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1957-1966, undated, (6 folders)
      - Washington, D.C., counsel for firm in, 1955-1959, undated, (2 folders)
    - Hart, Edward J., estate, 1937, 1948, 1955-1956, undated
    - Hempelmann, Elinor P. and Louis H.
      - Correspondence, 1952-1958
      - Legal documents, 1911, 1948-1956, undated, (2 folders)
    - Hertz, Helmut (Box 225)
      - Correspondence, 1955-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1949, 1955, undated
    - Hickok Manufacturing Co., 1957-1958
    - Hoover Commission Report See Container 158, Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government
    - Hunter, David
      - Correspondence, 1964-1965
      - Miscellany, 1965-1966, undated
    - Inauguration, Lyndon B. Johnson, 1964-1965
    - Inter-American Foundation for the Arts, 1965-1966, undated
    - International Cooperation Year (1965)
      - Citizens' Committee on Peacekeeping Operations
        - Correspondence, 1965-1966
        - Miscellany, 1965, n.d, (3 folders)
      - National Citizens' Commission (Box 226)
        - Correspondence, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1964-1965
        - Reports, 1965-1966, (3 folders)
    - International Executive Service Corps
      - Applicants, 1964
        - A-G, (3 folders)
        - H- Z, (6 folders) (Box 227)
      - Articles and speeches by Linowitz, 1963-1964, undated, (2 folders)
      - Board of Directors, members, 1964-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Bylaws and certificate of incorporation, 1964-1965, undated
      - Clippings, 1963-1966, undated
      - Congratulatory letters received, 1964 (Box 228)
      - Correspondence
        - 1963-1964, (11 folders)
        - 1965-1966, undated, (6 folders) (Box 229)
      - Executive Committee
        - Minutes of meetings
          - 1964, Mar.-1965, Mar., (7 folders)
          - 1965, June-1966, May, (8 folders) (Box 230)
          - 1966, Aug.-Oct., (2 folders) (Box 231)
        - Initial activities report, 1965
          - Vol. I, Operations, (4 folders)
          - Vol. II, Exhibits, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1964-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, undated
      - Organizing material, 1963-1966, undated, (5 folders) (Box 232)
      - Overseas Press Club of America, New York, N.Y., speech by Linowitz, 1964, undated
      - Planning documents, circa 1964
      - Projects, 1965
      - Staff, 1964-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Tax exemptions, 1964-1965 (Box 233)
    - International Industrial Conference, San Francisco, Calif., 1964-1965
    - International Marketing Institute, 1964-1966
    - International Rescue Committee, 1962-1966, undated
    - Interview requests, 1966
    - Israel, 1961-1966, undated
    - Jewett, C. Lincoln, 1957-1963
    - Jewish Young Men's and Women's Association, Rochester, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1950-1956
      - Miscellany, 1947-1948, undated
    - Jewish Community Council of Rochester, N.Y., 1961-1966
    - Jewish Theological Seminary of America, New York, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1962-1966
      - Interview and writings by Linowitz, 1952-1966, undated
    - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, Washington, D.C. (Box 234)
      - Board of Trustees
        - Correspondence, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
        - Meetings
          - 1964, July
          - 1964, Dec.
          - 1965, May
          - 1966, Feb.
      - Building
        - Correspondence, 1965-1966, (6 folders)
        - Design and construction, 1965-1966, undated, (2 folders) (Box 235)
        - Location, 1965, (2 folders)
        - Zoning, 1965
      - Concession agreement, 1965
      - General correspondence, 1964-1966, (3 folders)
      - Gifts and pledges
        - Comptroller general of the United States, 1965, (2 folders)
        - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 236)
        - Lists, 1964-1965, undated, (2 folders)
      - John F. Kennedy, Years of Lightning, Day of Drums (motion picture), distribution rights, 1965-1966
      - Miscellany, 1962-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - National Council of the Friends of the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1965-1966
    - Jones, Clarence B., 1965-1966
    - Juvenile delinquency
      - Conference, 1955
      - Correspondence, 1955-1958
      - Miscellany, 1955, undated
    - Kalb, Jack, 1966
    - Karp, Abraham J., 1962-1966
    - Kennedy, John F. (1917-1963), assassination (Box 237)
      - Clippings and printed matter, 1963
      - Condolences and memorials, 1960-1966, undated
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1963-1966, undated
    - Kiwanis Club of Rochester, N.Y., speech by Linowitz, 1962-1966, undated, (2 folders)
    - Kordite Corp., Macedon, N.Y., 1958-1963, (2 folders)
    - L. Atkin's Sons, 1949
    - Landers, Ann, 1966
    - Lanham, Charles Trueman, 1961-1966, (2 folders)
    - Lexington Advertiser, Lexington, Miss., 1963, undated
    - Liebmann, Felix G., 1958-1961, undated
    - Little Rock, Ark., school desegregation, 1957
    - Maintenance Methods, Inc., 1964
    - Marotta, Samuel, 1959
    - Marshak, Robert Eugene, 1950
    - Marshall, Frank, 1966, undated
    - Mayer, Martin (1928- ), 1966, undated (Box 238)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (1908-1957), 1954
    - McKinney, Robert M., 1963
    - McLuhan, Marshall, 1966
    - Meet the Press, 1965-1966
    - Mental health, 1951, 1954-1957, undated
    - Metropolitan Opera Association, New York, N.Y., 1963-1966
    - Meyer, Werner T., 1961-1962
    - Miller, Harlan Ward
      - Correspondence, 1958-1951, (2 folders)
      - Legal documents, 1946-1950, undated
    - Mobil Chemical Co., 1963-1964
    - Morgenthau, Robert M., 1958-1964
    - Moselowitz, Irving, 1948-1957, undated
    - National Alcohol Beverage Control Association, 1958
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1964
    - National Book Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 239)
    - National Businessmen's Council, 1966, undated
    - National Committee for Immigration Reform, 1953, 1958, 1965
    - National health care, income tax allowance plan
      - Clippings, 1949-1955, undated
      - Correspondence, 1949-1960, (9 folders)
      - Legislation, 1947-1951 (Box 240)
      - Miscellany, 1949-1956, undated, (2 folders)
      - Speeches and writings by Linowitz, 1946-1956, undated, (2 folders)
    - National Industrial Conference Board
      - Clippings, 1966, undated
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1964-1966, undated
      - Requests for copies of speech by Linowitz, 1966, (3 folders)
      - Speech by Linowitz (Apr. 21, 1966), 1965-1966, (3 folders) (Box 241)
    - National Planning Association, 1963-1966, undated, (2 folders)
    - Nixon, Justin Wroe, 1958-1959, undated
    - Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, 1963-1964
    - Office of Price Stabilization, 1950-1951
    - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1948
    - Overhage, Carl F. J.
      - Correspondence, 1948-1960, (5 folders)
      - Legal documents, 1941-1955, undated, (2 folders) (Box 242)
    - Pacem in Terris Convocation, New York, N.Y., 1965
    - Personal
      - Biographical material, 1960-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Clippings
        - Advisory Committee on International Organizations, State Department, 1961-1964, undated
        - American Jewish Committee, 1965-1966, undated
        - Antipoverty programs, 1963-1966, undated
        - Civil rights, undated
        - Democratic Party, 1966
        - Education, 1953, 1960-1966, undated
        - Enterprise Fellowships, 1965, undated
        - Frank Irvine Lecture, 1966, undated
        - Governor of New York, possible candidate, 1966, (3 folders)
        - International Executive Service Corps, 1964-1965, undated
        - Life magazine, 1966
        - Miscellaneous, 1950-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - National Businessmen's Council, 1966, undated (Box 243)
        - National Committee for International Development, 1953, 1961-1966
        - National Industrial Conference Board, 1966
        - New York Times Magazine, 1966
        - President's General Advisory Committee on Foreign Assistance Programs, 1965
        - Saturday Review, 1965
        - Trips, 1955, 1960-1963
        - United Nations, 1949, 1952-1965, undated
        - Washington, D.C., 1966
        - Xerox Corp.
          - Chairman, Board of the Directors, election, 1959-1966, undated
          - Miscellany, 1954, 1961-1966, undated
      - Governor of New York, possible candidate
        - Background briefing books, 1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Correspondence, 1966, (2 folders)
        - Notes, undated
        - Radio and television broadcast reports, 1966
      - Gridiron Club dinner, Washington, D.C., 1962
      - Miscellany, 1947-1966, undated
      - Office of Price Administration, Washington, D.C., 1942-1945, undated (Box 244)
      - Organization of American States
        - Congratulations received, lists, 1966
        - General correspondence, 1966, (2 folders)
        - Job seekers, 1966
      - Phi Beta Kappa, 1962, undated
      - Public service, 1962-1966
      - Rank Organisation, London, England, 1963-1966
      - Real estate
        - East Avenue, Rochester, N.Y.
          - Correspondence, 1957-1966, undated, (2 folders)
          - Legal documents, 1931-1958, undated
        - Egypt Valley Road, Bristol, N.Y., 1965-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Grosvenor Road, Brighton, N.Y., 1956-1957
        - Monteroy Road, Brighton, N.Y., 1945-1958, undated
      - Sutherland, Andrew R., 1960-1961, undated (Box 245)
      - Sutherland, Arthur E., 1962-1966, undated
      - Sutherland, Elizabeth, 1962-1965
      - Sutherland, Linowitz and Williams (law firm), Rochester, N.Y., 1957-1958, undated
      - Taxes, 1952, 1961-1962
      - United States Navy, 1943-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Wilson, Joseph C. (1909-1971)
        - Clippings, 1959-1966
        - Estate
          - Correspondence, 1953-1964
          - Legal documents, 1949-1964
        - General correspondence, 1956-1966, (3 folders)
        - Marie C. and Joseph C. Wilson Foundation, 1963-1966
        - Property purchased
          - Correspondence, 1964
          - Legal documents, 1955, 1964, undated
        - Property transferred, 1948-1957, undated (Box 246)
      - Wilson, Joseph R., 1930, 1949-1953, undated
      - Xerox Corp.
        - Investment group, 1957-1966, (2 folders)
        - Resignation, 1966
        - Security clearance, 1954, 1960-1963
      - Xerox International, 1966
    - Peyser, Seymour M., 1965-1966
    - Pfaudler Permutit, Inc.
      - Enamelled Metal Products Corp., 1933-1957, undated, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1962, (3 folders)
      - Japan, 1945, 1957-1958, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1955-1962, undated (Box 247)
      - Panama, 1956-1957, undated
    - “Pigeon hole parking” building proposal, Rochester, N.Y., 1955
    - Piper, Homer, 1955
    - Political campaigns
      - 1956
        - Congressional elections, 1956, undated
        - New York State Committee for Stevenson and Kefauver
          - Correspondence, 1956, undated, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1950-1956, undated
          - Printed matter, 1956, undated
          - Speech and notes by Linowitz, (2 folders)
      - 1958-1960, (2 folders)
      - 1964
        - National Independent Committee for President Johnson and Senator Humphrey, 1964-1965, (3 folders)
        - Republican National Convention, San Francisco, Calif., 1964
        - Other campaigns, 1964 (Box 248)
      - 1966
    - Pollution, 1966
    - Powers Hotel, Rochester, N.Y.
      - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1953, undated
      - Correspondence, 1947-1953, undated, (4 folders)
      - Missing suitcase, 1946-1947, undated
    - Powott Corp., New York, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1947-1948
      - Legal and financial documents, 1942-1948, undated, (2 folders)
    - Present, Beryl M., 1956-1960, undated
    - President's Club, Washington, D.C., 1963-1966
    - Publishers
      - Life magazine, “close-up” article on Linowitz, 1966, undated, (3 folders)
      - Look magazine, 1965-1966 (Box 249)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961-1966, undated, (3 folders)
      - New York Times, 1965-1966
      - New York Times Magazine, profile of Linowitz, 1966, (3 folders)
      - Newsweek, 1965-1966
      - Reader's Digest, 1966
      - Show magazine, 1963
      - Saturday Review, 1962-1966, undated
      - Think magazine, 1964-1965
      - Time magazine, 1964-1966
      - Washington Post, 1966, undated
      - Woman's Day magazine, 1966
    - Rank Xerox (Box 250)
      - Rank Organisation
        - Annual reports
          - Correspondence, 1964-1966
          - Printed copies, 1959-1966, (3 folders)
        - Board of Directors
          - Correspondence, 1962-1966, (3 folders)
          - Minutes of meetings
            - 1963, Sept.-1964, Apr., (2 folders)
            - 1964, June-1966, Sept., (8 folders) (Box 251)
          - Reports pertaining to meetings
            - 1962, Oct.-1963, Nov., (2 folders)
            - 1963, Dec.-1965, Mar., (10 folders) (Box 252)
            - 1965, Apr.-1966, Jan., (8 folders) (Box 253)
            - 1966, Mar.-Oct., (5 folders) (Box 254)
        - Clippings, 1955-1965, undated
        - Correspondence
          - General
            - 1955-1963, (3 folders)
            - 1964-1966, (7 folders) (Box 255)
          - Personal
            - 1959-1962, (2 folders)
            - 1963-1966 (Box 256)
        - Davis, John
          - Correspondence, 1965-1966
          - Speeches by Davis, 1960-1966, (2 folders)
        - Joseph Sebag and Co., 1966
        - Miscellany, 1959-1966, undated See also Oversize, (3 folders)
        - Monopolies Commission, undated
        - Research Committee, 1965
        - Sealing Committee, 1963-1966, (8 folders) (Box 257)
      - Xerox Corp.
        - Annual reports
          - Mailing lists, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
          - Printed copies
            - 1951-1959
            - 1960-1966, (3 folders) (Box 258)
        - Electro-Optical Systems, 1963-1966, undated
        - Miscellany, 1955-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Personal correspondence
          - 1955, May-1965, Oct., (4 folders)
          - 1965, Nov.-1966, Oct., (2 folders) (Box 259)
        - Travel
          - Chronological file
            - 1955, May-1959, June, (10 folders)
            - 1960, Apr.-1961, May, (10 folders) (Box 260)
            - 1961, Nov.-1962, Apr., (11 folders) (Box 261)
            - 1963, Jan.-1965, Feb., (14 folders) (Box 262)
            - 1965, Apr.-1966, Oct., (14 folders) (Box 263)
          - Personal notes and comments (Box 264)
            - Belgium, 1958, undated
            - England, 1957-1958, 1965-1966, undated
            - Europe, 1958
            - France, 1955-1960, undated
            - Germany, 1955-1960, undated
            - Israel, 1958
            - Italy, 1955-1966, undated
            - Japan, 1961
            - Miscellaneous, undated
            - Netherlands, 1955-1957
            - Spain and Portugal, 1959, undated
            - Switzerland, 1955-1957, undated
    - Qualtop Beverages, Inc., 1950, undated
    - Ray Hylan School of Aeronautics v. Di Battisto, 1953-1955
    - Ray Hylan School of Aeronautics v. United States, 1950-1954, (2 folders)
    - Recommendations
      - Academic, 1962-1966, (2 folders)
      - Others, 1962-1966, undated, (2 folders) (Box 265)
    - Religion, 1955, 1966
    - Rent control, 1940, 1946-1947, 1955, undated
    - Robeson Cutlery, Perry, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1951-1953
      - Miscellany, 1951-1952, undated
    - Rochester, N.Y.
      - Citizens Committee of Sponsors for the Montgomery Neighborhood Center, 1960
      - Citizens Committee on Housing
        - Correspondence, 1951-1959, undated, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1951-1954, undated, (2 folders)
      - Citizens Committee to Investigate Rochester Hospital Costs, 1951, undated
      - Hospitals, 1959, undated
      - Sister cities program
        - Japan, proposed cities
          - Correspondence, 1959-1960
          - Printed matter, 1960, 1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Rennes, France (Box 266)
          - Clippings, 1957-1964, undated, (2 folders)
          - Correspondence
            - 1956, July-1960, June, (9 folders)
            - 1960, July-1966, Aug., (8 folders) (Box 267)
          - Miscellany, 1958-1965, undated, (2 folders)
          - Travel to Rennes and Israel
            - Miscellany, 1952-1960, undated
            - Writings and notes by Linowitz, 1955-1958, undated, (2 folders) (Box 268)
        - Other cities, 1964
    - Rochester Applied Science Associates, Rochester, N.Y., 1963, undated
    - Rochester Chamber of Commerce, Rochester, N.Y.
      - Board of Trustees
        - Meetings
          - 1958, Jan.-1959, Oct., (18 folders)
          - 1959, Nov.-1961, Jan., (10 folders) (Box 269)
        - Nominating Committee, 1958-1959
        - Officers and committees, 1958
      - Brotherhood Week, 1948-1959, undated
      - Clippings, 1957-1959, undated
      - Committee on the Out-of-Town Acquisition of Rochester Companies
        - Correspondence, 1955-1959, (3 folders)
        - Reports and printed matter, 1955-1959, undated, (2 folders)
      - Dinners (Box 270)
        - Annual
          - 1959, 1966, (3 folders)
        - Folsom, Marian Bayard, welcome-home dinner
          - Correspondence, 1955-1958, (4 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1955-1958, undated
      - General correspondence
        - 1951, June-1955, Aug., (5 folders)
        - 1955, Sept.-1958, Jan., (12 folders) (Box 271)
        - 1958, Feb.-1962, Sept., (11 folders) (Box 272)
        - 1962, Oct.-1966, Oct., (2 folders) (Box 273)
      - Miscellany, 1938, 1957-1964, undated, (2 folders)
      - Rochester Bureau of Municipal Research, Rochester, N.Y., 1958
      - Special Capital Fund and Special Maintenance Fund Campaign, 1959
      - Speeches and writings
        - By Linowitz, 1952-1959, undated
        - By others, 1952, undated
      - Transportation Club, 1953, undated
    - Rochester Civic Music Association, Rochester, N.Y., 1956-1966, (2 folders)
    - Rochester Employing Printers v. Rochester Printing Crafts Union, 1949
    - Rochester Hospital Fund, Rochester, N.Y., 1962-1963
    - Rochester Hospital Service, New York, N.Y., 1954-1956, undated (Box 274)
    - Rochester Hotel Association, Rochester, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1949-1954, undated, (2 folders)
      - Labor contract negotiations, 1947-1952, undated, (7 folders)
    - Rochester Institute of International Affairs, Rochester, N.Y., 1948-1953, undated
    - Rochester Orthoptic Center, Rochester, N.Y., 1949-1962, (2 folders)
    - Rochester Rotary Club, Rochester, N.Y.
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966
      - Speeches by Linowitz, 1954-1965 (Box 275)
    - Rochester Town and Country, Inc.
      - Correspondence, 1950-1966, undated, (5 folders)
      - Financial statements, 1951-1963, (2 folders)
      - Legal documents, 1950-1959, undated, (3 folders)
    - Rosenthal, David, 1947-1949, undated
    - Salk, Jonas, 1966, undated
    - Salvation Army Building Fund, Rochester, N.Y., 1952-1953, undated (Box 276)
    - Samuels, Howard Joseph, 1962-1966, undated
    - Schmeck, Dorothy, 1957
    - Self Winding Alarm Clock Co., New York, N.Y., 1963-1964
    - Seneca Hotel, Rochester, N.Y., 1953-1954
    - Shaw, Maud, memoirs
      - Copies of draft
        - Vol. I, 1965, Oct. 18, (2 folders)
        - Vol. II, 1965, Oct. 20, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
      - Notes, undated
      - Serialization, 1966 (Box 277)
    - Shuron Optical Co., Rochester, N.Y., 1958-1960
    - Society for Advancement of Management
      - Correspondence, 1964-1965, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1963-1966, undated, (2 folders)
    - Stanway, Joseph, 1957, undated
    - Stern, Isaac (1920-2001), 1960-1966, undated, (2 folders)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E. (1900-1965)
      - Adlai E. Stevenson College, Santa Cruz, Calif., circa 1966
      - Adlai E. Stevenson Memorial Fund
        - Correspondence, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1965-1966 (Box 278)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1966, undated
      - Miscellany, 1956-1965, undated
      - School dedication, Rochester, N.Y., 1961-1965, undated
    - Swett, Albert H., 1966
    - Television
      - Community Broadcasting, Inc., 1961-1965, undated
      - Correspondence
        - 1949-1959, (6 folders)
        - 1960-1965, undated, (4 folders) (Box 279)
      - Miscellany, 1955-1958, 1964-1966
      - Programs proposed, 1951-1957, 1965, undated, (3 folders)
      - WVET
        - Board of Directors, 1949-1952, undated
        - Collier, Stanley, 1949-1950, undated, (2 folders)
        - Financial reports
          - 1948-1949
          - 1950-1961, undated, (2 folders) (Box 280)
        - Miscellany, 1947-1957, undated, (3 folders)
    - Termatto, Connie, 1962
    - Three Hour Laundry and Dry Cleaning Stores, Inc., 1958-1958
    - Timely Clothes, Inc., 1959-1961
    - Tomaselli, Marjorie, 1956-1959, undated
    - Twentieth Century Fund
      - Correspondence, 1963-1964
      - Proposed conference, 1963, undated, (2 folders)
    - Union Steel Chest Corp., 1959
    - United Artist Corp., 1962-1966
    - United Jewish Welfare Fund
      - Correspondence
        - 1947-1950, (2 folders)
        - 1951-1966, undated, (2 folders) (Box 281)
      - Miscellany, 1947-1958, undated, (2 folders)
    - United Nations
      - American Association for the United Nations
        - Board of Directors
          - Correspondence
            - 1957-1964, (7 folders)
            - 1965-1966, (2 folders) (Box 282)
          - Miscellany, 1961-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Bylaws, 1962-1965, undated, (2 folders)
        - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1953, undated, (3 folders)
        - Conferences
          - Correspondence, 1953-1954, 1962
          - Miscellany, 1952-1962, undated, (2 folders)
        - Executive Committee
          - Correspondence, 1964-1965, (2 folders)
          - Minutes of meetings, 1964-1966, (3 folders) (Box 283)
        - General correspondence
          - 1952, Sept.-1957, Nov., (10 folders)
          - 1958, Jan.-1965, May, (14 folders) (Box 284)
          - 1965, June-1966, Dec., undated, (3 folders) (Box 285)
        - Merger and Joint Operations Committee
          - Correspondence, 1963-1964
            - Set I, (4 folders)
            - Set II, (3 folders)
          - Meetings and reports
            - 1963, Jan.-1964, Feb., (4 folders)
            - 1964, Mar.-May, undated, (3 folders) (Box 286)
        - Policy Committee, 1954-1960
        - Position papers, 1960-1962, undated, (3 folders)
        - Roosevelt, Eleanor (1884-1962)
          - Correspondence, 1952-1962, (5 folders)
          - Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation, 1964-1965
      - Atomic energy, 1953, undated (Box 287)
      - Charter, 1945-1961, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1945-1965, undated, (2 folders)
      - Rochester Association for the United Nations, Rochester, N.Y.
        - Board of Directors, 1949-1952, undated, (2 folders)
        - Correspondence
          - 1952, Mar.-1953, June, (6 folders)
          - 1953, July-1966, May, (9 folders) (Box 288)
        - Miscellany, 1947-1962, undated, (2 folders)
        - Policy Committee, 1948-1958, undated, (2 folders)
      - Speeches and writings by Linowitz (Box 289)
        - Correspondence and clippings, 1949-1961, undated
        - Notes and outlines, 1861, 1948-1950, undated, (3 folders)
        - Text, 1949-1953, undated, (2 folders)
      - United Nations Conference on the Application of Science and Technology for the Benefit of the Less Developed Areas, Geneva